[{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980253179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":23994,"timeElapsed":72649},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":12983,"timeElapsed":85633},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":11521,"timeElapsed":97155},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980283279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5593,"timeElapsed":102749},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980288513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5233,"timeElapsed":107983},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":15011,"timeElapsed":122995},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7588,"timeElapsed":130584},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":16155,"timeElapsed":146740},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6785,"timeElapsed":153525},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":24457,"timeElapsed":180385},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":6424,"timeElapsed":186810},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":18385,"timeElapsed":205196},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5793,"timeElapsed":210989},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":7078,"timeElapsed":218068},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":26051,"timeElapsed":244120},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6716,"timeElapsed":250837},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":8031,"timeElapsed":258868},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5396,"timeElapsed":264265},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":14729,"timeElapsed":283680},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9459,"timeElapsed":293139},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":8618,"timeElapsed":301758},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6593,"timeElapsed":308352},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4795,"timeElapsed":313148},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7032,"timeElapsed":320181},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5827,"timeElapsed":326009},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7616,"timeElapsed":333626},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4344,"timeElapsed":337972},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7685,"timeElapsed":347337},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9603,"timeElapsed":356941},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7809,"timeElapsed":364751},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980550959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5677,"timeElapsed":370429},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4012,"timeElapsed":374441},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7362,"timeElapsed":381804},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3401,"timeElapsed":385206},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":8915,"timeElapsed":394122},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4708,"timeElapsed":398831},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8787,"timeElapsed":409303},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3955,"timeElapsed":413259},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3674,"timeElapsed":416935},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":420286},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5139,"timeElapsed":425426},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7301,"timeElapsed":432728},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2925,"timeElapsed":435655},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629340,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13154,"timeElapsed":448810},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9585,"timeElapsed":458395},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4143,"timeElapsed":462539},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":12401,"timeElapsed":476717},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5970,"timeElapsed":482688},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4561,"timeElapsed":487249},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5561,"timeElapsed":492811},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4665,"timeElapsed":497478},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7637,"timeElapsed":505117},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3678,"timeElapsed":508795},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":7301,"timeElapsed":516097},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5180,"timeElapsed":521277},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":12240,"timeElapsed":535132},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8636,"timeElapsed":543768},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4580,"timeElapsed":548349},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980732622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3743,"timeElapsed":552092},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980738906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6282,"timeElapsed":558376},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6524,"timeElapsed":564902},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6242,"timeElapsed":571144},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9008,"timeElapsed":580153},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5595,"timeElapsed":585749},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9784,"timeElapsed":597317},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4349,"timeElapsed":601667},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3695,"timeElapsed":605363},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":608376},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795667,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6760,"timeElapsed":615137},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6282,"timeElapsed":621419},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5748,"timeElapsed":627168},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4371,"timeElapsed":631541},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5651,"timeElapsed":637193},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3720,"timeElapsed":640915},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10449,"timeElapsed":653088},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3977,"timeElapsed":657066},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7532,"timeElapsed":664599},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4244,"timeElapsed":668844},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3943,"timeElapsed":672787},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8535,"timeElapsed":681323},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4013,"timeElapsed":685337},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7403,"timeElapsed":692740},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3565,"timeElapsed":696306},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980895480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":17067,"timeElapsed":714950},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8504,"timeElapsed":723456},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4670,"timeElapsed":728127},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5524,"timeElapsed":733652},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4339,"timeElapsed":737992},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":7059,"timeElapsed":745051},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":748396},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":7753,"timeElapsed":756150},{"subjectID":"q7zda7fh87","prolificID":"665629a30c7e3f40e8f3d1d5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b242e75ced714536ccb2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980941664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4983,"timeElapsed":761134}]